A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.38 (A2013) FA473
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2013.097: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2011; AC_2013_097; 24.89 Cubic Feet 19 standard record storage boxes, R4145-R4163; 19 standard record storage boxes, R4145-R4163
  - Health Equity (HE), AC_2013_097_1; 14.41 Cubic Feet 11 record storage boxes
    - 2006 HE 013 - CONSULTATION OF INVESTMENT IN HEALTH PROMOTION (VIETNAM) - COMMUNICATION AND DISSEMINATION OF RESEARCH ON GENDER, SEXUALITY AND SEXUAL HEALTH, 2002-2009 (Box R4153)
    - 2006 HE 013 - Culture, Health and Sexuality - Published Material, 2002-2009; 2013:097:013 (Box R4153)
    - 2003 HE 067 - Gender, Sexuality and Sexual Health - Digital, 2002-2009; 2013:097:014 (Box R4153)
    - 2003 HE 067 - Link between Genders. Sexual and Reproductive Health in Vietnam - Digital, 2002-2009; 2013:097:052 (Box R4153)
    - 2003 HE 067 - Gender, Women's Empowerment and Reproductive Health in 4 Vietnamese Communities - Digital, 2002-2009; 2013:097:015 (Box R4153)
    - 2003 HE 067 - Consultation of Investment in Health Promotion; Gender, Sexuality and Sexual Health - Digital, 2002-2009; 2013:097:016 (Box R4153)
    - 2006 HE 014 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - MASTER'S DEGREE PROGRAM IN HEALTH SOCIAL SCIENCES; CONFERENCE, 2002-2009 (Box R4153)
    - Gender and Sexuality and their implications for sexual and reproductive health including HIV/AIDS: A case study of young female factory wokrers in Vientiane, Lao PDR - Published Material, 2002-2009; 2013:097:017 (Box R4153)
    - Lifestyles, sexuallity, and cultural beliefs related to unsafe sexual practices among youth in Peri-urban Yangon, Myanmar - Published Material, 2002-2009; 2013:097:018 (Box R4153)
    - Health Social Science; Working Papers in Sexual and Reproductive Health - Published Material, 2002-2009; 2013:097:019 (Box R4153)
    - 2006 HE 015 - RAKS THAI FOUNDATION (THAILAND) - AFRICA-ASIA INTER-EXCHANGE LEARNING COMMUNITIES NETWORKS ON AIDS, 2005-2008 (Box R4153)
    - 2006 HE 016 - INTERNATIONAL HEALTH POLICY PROGRAM (THAILAND) - ASIAN-PACIFIC ACTION ALLIANCE ON HRH (Box R4153)
    - 2006 HE 018 - LUNDY FOUNDATION - EVALUATION OF IDWELI CHILDREN'S HOME IN TANZANIA, 2005-2007 (Box R4153)
    - 2006 HE 021 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - ELECTRONIC MEDICAL RECORDS FOR HIV/AIDS, 2006-2011 (Box R4154)
    - 2006 HE 022 - MEDICAL RESEARCH COUNCIL (ENGLAND) - DART HIV/AIDS TRIAL COORDINATION IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA (2 FOLDERS), 2001-2010 (Box R4154)
    - 2006 HE 023 - CENTRE FOR THE MANAGEMENT OF IP IN HEALTH R and D (ENGLAND) - GENERAL SUPPORT (1 and 1 SUPPL.), 2002-2007 (Box R4154)
    - Handbook of Best Practices for Management of Intellectual Property in Helath Research and Development - Published Material, 2002-2007; 2013:097:020 (Box R4154)
    - MIHR/MRC IP Specialization Workshop, Hermanus, South Africa 17-20 February 2003 - Digital, 2002-2007; 2013:097:021 (Box R4154)
    - 2007 HE 001 - GLOBAL FUND TO FIGHT AIDS, TUBERCULOSIS and MALARIA (SWITZERLAND) - AIDS PHOTODOCUMENTARY, 2007-2009 (Box R4154)
    - 2007 HE 001 - Access to Life - Published Material, 2007-2009; 2013:097:022 (Box R4154)
    - 2007 HE 003 - CENTRE FOR THE MANAGEMENT OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY IN HEALTH RESEARCH and DEVELOPMENT (ENGLAND) - PUBLIC SECTOR TECHNOLOGIES AND PRODUCTS DEVELOPMENT, 2003-2007 (Box R4155)
    - 2007 HE 003 - Intellectual Property Management in Health and Agricultural Innovation - Published Material, 2003-2007; 2013:097:023 (Box R4155)
    - 2004 HE 050 - Institute for Global Ethics: Cornerstones for Ethical foundations, 2003-2007; 2013:097:024 (Box R4155)
    - 2007 HE 003 - Intellectual Property Management in Health and Agricultural Innovation - Published material, 2003-2007; 2013:097:025 (Box R4155)
    - 2007 HE 003 - Intellectural Property Management in Health and Agricultual Innovation: a handbook of best practices - Published Material (2 volumes), 2003-2007; 2013:097:051 (Box R4155)
    - 2007 HE 004 - CAMBODIA - WOMEN'S AND VETERANS' AFFAIRS (MINISTRY OF) - WOMEN'S VOICES RADIO PROGRAM, 2003-2007 (Box R4155)
    - 2007 HE 005 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - AMERICA'S VITAL INTEREST IN GLOBAL HEALTH REPORT, 2007-2009 (Box R4155)
    - 2007 HE 007 - RAND CORPORATION - DATA ON DART TRIALS IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2007-2010 (Box R4155)
    - 2007 HE 009 - INDEPTH NETWORK (GHANA) - BUSINESS PLANNING CONSULTANCY, 2007-2008 (Box R4155)
    - 2007 HE 010 - UNION FOR AFRICAN POPULATION STUDIES (GHANA) - FIFTH AFRICAN POPULATION CONFERENCE, 2007-2008 (Box R4155)
    - 2007 HE 011 - CONCEPT FOUNDATION (THAILAND) - MIHR TRANSITION, 2007-2010 (Box R4155)
    - 2008 HE 001 - CABINET OFFICE, GOVERNMENT OF JAPAN - HIDEYO NOGUCHI AFRICA PRIZE, 2006-2010 (Box R4155)
    - 2008 HE 001 - Prix Hideyo Noguchi pour l'Afrique - Digital, 2006-2010; 2013:097:026 (Box R4155)
    - 2008 HE 002 - INDEPTH NETWORK (GHANA) - GENERAL SUPPORT (2 FOLDERS), 2002-2011 (Box R4155)
  - Global Inclusion (GI), AC_2013_097_2; 13.1 Cubic Feet 10 record storage boxes
    - 2000 GI 010 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - COMMON SECURITY FORUM, 1999-2004 (Box R4156)
    - 2000 GI 037 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - REGIONAL CONFLICT FORMATIONS IN ASIA AND AFRICA, 2000-2007 (Box R4156)
    - 2000 GI 056 - (GLOBAL INCLUSION) - MINORITY RIGHTS ISSUES, 2000-2004 (Box R4156)
    - 2000 GI 057 - (GLOBAL INCLUSION) - ARMED GROUPS AND HUMAN RIGHTS, 2001-2005 (Box R4156)
    - 2000 GI 075 - CENTRE FOR SCIENCE AND ENVIRONMENT (INDIA) - COMMUNITY-BASE WATER MANAGEMENT, 2000-2005 (Box R4156)
    - 2000 GI 097 - PANOS INSTITUTE (ENGLAND) - PUBLIC DEBATE ON PLANT BIOTECHNOLOGY IN KENYA AND ZAMBIA, 2000-2005 (Box R4156)
    - 2000 GI 109 - UNIVERSITY OF COSTA RICA - TRANGENIC RICE CULTIVAR IN LATIN AMERICA, 2000-2007 (Box R4156)
    - 2000 GI 110 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - TRANSGENIC RICE CULTIVARS IN LATIN AMERICA, 2000-2006 (Box R4156)
    - 2000 GI 111 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT (CANADA) - CAPACITY BUILDING FOR TRADE AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT, 2000-2004 (Box R4156)
    - 2000 GI 119 - SOUTH CENTRE (SWITZERLAND) - MONOGRAPH ON PUBLIC HEALTH AND PATENT LEGISLATION IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2000-2006 (Box R4157)
    - 2000 GI 119 - Protection and Promotion of Traditional Medicine - Published Material, 2000-2006; 2013:097:027 (Box R4157)
    - 2000 GI 119 - Integrando la Salud Publica en la Legislation Sobre Patents de los Paises en Desarrollo - Published Material, 2000-2006; 2013:097:028 (Box R4157)
    - 2000 GI 119 - Protection of Data Submitted for the Registration of Pharmaceuticals - Published Material, 2000-2006; 2013:097:029 (Box R4157)
    - 2000 GI 119 - Integrating Publich Health Concerns into Patent Legislation in Developing Countries, 2000-2006; 2013:097:030 (Box R4157)
    - 2000 GI 120 - NAUTILUS OF AMERICA - FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM ON INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY AND SECURITY, 2000-2006 (Box R4157)
    - 2000 GI 126 - CROPPER FOUNDATION (TRINIDAD and TOBAGO) - CONFERENCE ON PUBLIC POLICY, ENVIRONMENT AND EQUITY, 2000-2004 (Box R4157)
    - 2001 GI 006 - (GLOBAL INCLUSION) - GOVERNANCE OF SCIENCE FOR THE PUBLIC GOOD, 2001-2005 (Box R4157)
    - 2001 GI 007 - HESPERIAN FOUNDATION - HEALTH AND SAFETY MANUAL FOR WORKERS, 2000-2005 (Box R4157)
    - 2001 GI 057 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - INTERNATIONAL DIALOGUE ON GMO REGULATION (1 and 2 SUPPL.), 2000-2006 (Box R4157)
    - 2001 GI 084 - (GLOBAL INCLUSION) - GLOBAL TRENDS MONITORING AND ANALYSIS GROUP, 2001-2006 (Box R4158)
    - 2001 GI 092 - NEELAN TIRUCHELVAM TRUST (SRI LANKA) - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2001-2007 (Box R4158)
    - 2001 GI 100 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR RESEARCH ON WOMEN - WOMEN'S ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL STATUS, 2001-2004 (Box R4158)
    - 2001 GI 107 - CRISIS MANAGEMENT INITIATIVE (FINLAND) - NORTH-SOUTH FORUM, 2001-2004 (Box R4158)
    - 2001 GI 113 - TUFTS UNIVERSITY - VOLUME ON HUMAN RIGHTS AND CONFLICT RESOLUTION, 2001-2005 (Box R4158)
    - 2001 GI 114 - TRINITY COLLEGE - POLICY DEBATES ON HAITI, 2001-2004 (Box R4158)
    - 2002 GI 004 - KCTS TELEVISION - DOCUMETARY ON WORLD HUNGER, 2002-2006 (Box R4158)
    - 2002 GI 004 - Silent Killer: The Unfinished Campaign Against Hunger - Digital, 2002-2006; 2013:097:031 (Box R4158)
    - 2002 GI 006 - SYRACUSE UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE ON GENETICALLY MODIFIED WITH FOODS FOCUS ON SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2001-2004 (Box R4158)
    - 2002 GI 007 - (GLOBAL INCLUSION) - CONFERENCE AND CD-ROM ON GLOBAL BIOTECHNOLOGY DIALOGUES, 2003-2005 (Box R4158)
    - 2002 GI 008 - INTERNATIONAL PLANT GENETIC RESOURCES INSTITUTE (ITALY) - GENETIC RESOURCES POLICY INITIATIVE (2 FOLDERS), 2001-2009 (Box R4159)
    - 2002 GI 008 - GRPI Products CD burned September 2009, 2001-2009; 2013:097:032 (Item 2013:097:032)
    - 2002 GI 009 - CENTER FOR THE APPLICATION OF MOLECULAR BIOLOGY TO INTERNATIONAL AGRICULTURE (AUSTRALIA) - CAMBIA INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RESOURCE, 2001-2005 (Box R4159)
    - 2002 GI 2009 - Cambia IP Resource CD Archive of Website - Digital, 2001-2009; 2013:097:033 (Item 2013:097:033)
    - 2002 GI 014 - CONSUMERS UNION - TRANSATLANTIC CONSUMER DIALOGUE PROOJECT ON INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY, 2002-2004 (Box R4159)
    - 2002 GI 014 The Trans Atlantic Consumer Dialogue (TACD) Workshop - Digital, 2002-2004; 2013:097:034 (Item 2013:097:034)
    - 2002 GI 015 - AMERICAN ASSOCIATION FOR THE ADVANCEMENT OF SCIENCE - SCIENCE AND IPR ISSUES, 2002-2007 (Box R4159)
    - 2002 GI 016 - UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMME - REPORT ON TRADE AND HUMAN DEVELOPMENT, 2002-2006 (Box R4159)
    - 2002 GI 016 - Making Global Trade Work for People - Published Material, 2002-2006; 2013:097:035 (Item 2013:097:035)
    - 2002 GI 016 - Making Global Trade Work for People - Published Material, 2002-2006; 2013:097:036 (Item 2013:097:036)
    - 2002 GI 021 - HEARTLAND ALLIANCE - ENLACES AMERICA PROGRAM, 2002-2004 (Box R4159)
    - 2002 GI 022 - INTERHEMISPHERIC RESOURCES CENTER - ECONOMIC INTEGRATIONS IN THE AMERICAS, 2002-2005 (Box R4160)
    - 2002 GI 024 - BRITAIN YEARLY MEETING (ENGLAND) - WTO AND TRIPS PROCESS, 2000-2006 (Box R4160)
    - 2002 GI 026 - MEXICAN ASSOCIATION OF SOCIAL SECTOR CREDIT UNIONS - BANKING SERVICES IN TRANSNATIONAL COMMUNITIES, 2000-2006 (Box R4160)
    - 2002 GI 027 - RADIO BILINGUE - BINATIONAL RADIO PROGRAMMING, 2002-2006 (Box R4160)
    - 2002 GI 027 - Linea Abierta, President Vicente Fox Visits California, 3/26/01 - Digital, 2002-2006; 2013:097:037 (Item 2013:097:037)
    - 2002 GI 028 - LONDON SCHOOL OF ECONOMICS AND POLITICAL SCIENCE, UNIVERSITY OF LONDON (ENGLAND) - TRENDS AND IDEAS IN GLOBAL CIVIL SOCIETY, 2002-2004 (Box R4160)
    - 2002 GI 029 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - SECURITY AND MULTILATERALISM, 2002-2005 (Box R4160)
    - 2002 GI 032 - SYNERGOS INSTITUTE - STRENGTHENING COMMUNITY FOUNDATIONS IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2001-2003 (Box R4160)
    - 2002 GI 034 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR TRADE AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT (SWITZERLAND) - BC TEAM: FRATI GLOBAL DIALOGUE ON IP: STRENGTHENING IP LEADERSHIP, 2002-2006 (Box R4160)
    - 2002 GI 036 - INTER-AMERICAN DIALOGUE - TRANSNATIONAL COMMUNITIES, 2002-2006 (Box R4160)
    - 2002 GI 039 - INTER-AMERICAN DIALOGUE - REMITTANCES FROM IMMIGRANTS AND ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL DEVELOPMENT IN THEIR REGION, 2002-2006 (Box R4160)
    - 2002 GI 040 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - CONFLICT PREVENTION AND PEACE FORUM, 2002-2005 (Box R4160)
    - 2002 GI 041 - CARTER CENTER - GLOBAL DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVE, 2002-2006 (Box R4160)
    - 2002 GI 041 - Development Cooperation Forum: Human Security and the Future of Development Cooperation - Published Material, 2002-2006; 2013:097:038 (Item 2013:097:038)
    - 2002 GI 042 - INTERACTION: AMERICAN COUNCIL FOR VOLUNTARY INTERNATIONAL ACTION - INTER-AMERICAN DEVELOPMEN BANK-CIVIL SOCIETY INITIATIVE, 2002-2005 (Box R4161)
    - 2002 GI 045 - EL COLEGIO DE MEXICO - ALTERNATIVE POLICIES FOR SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT, 2002-2004 (Box R4161)
    - 2002 GI 048 - UNIVERSITY OF BRITISH COLUMBIA (CANADA) - WORKSHOPS ON CIVIL WAR AND THE RESEARCH AND POLICY COMMUNITIES, 2002-2005 (Box R4161)
    - Human Security Report 2005, War and Peace in the 21st Century - Published Material, 2002-2005; 2013:097:039 (Item 2013:097:039)
    - 2002 GI 049 - PACIFIC COUNCIL ON INTERNATIONA POLICY - TRANSNATIONAL DYNAMICS IN NORTH AMERICA, 2002-2005 (Box R4161)
    - 2002 GI 050 - FORO NACIONAL/INTERNATIONAL (PERU) - KNOWLEDGE FOR DEVELOPMENT IN THE 21ST CENTURY, 2002-2004 (Box R4161)
    - 2002 GI 051 - EL RESCATE - SALVADORANS AND COMMUNITY REMITTANCES, 2002-2006 (Box R4161)
    - 2002 GI 052 - UNIVERSITY OF BRITISH COLUMBIA (CANADA) - CURBING HUMAN RIGHTS VIOLATIONS BY NON-STATE ARMEND GROUPS, 2002-2006 (Box R4161)
    - 2002 GI 053 - SUSTAINABLE SCIENCES INSTITUTE - BIOPOLITICS OF RISK, 2002-2004 (Box R4161)
    - 2002 GI 054 - (GLOBAL INCLUSION) - DIALOGUE ON BIOTECHNOLOGY (1 and 1 SUPPL. FOLDER), 2000-2005 (Box R4162)
    - 2002 GI 055 - (GLOBAL INCLUSION) - KNOWLEDGE AND INNOVATION FOR DEVELOPMENT, 2002-2005 (Box R4162)
    - 2002 GI 057 - SOUTH CENTRE (SWITZERLAND) - DEVELOPING COUNTRIES' ACCESS TO MEDICINE, 2002-2006 (Box R4162)
    - 2002 GI 057 - Utilizing Trips Flexibilities for Public Health Protection Through South-South Regional Frameworks - Published Material, 2002-2006; 2013:097:040 (Item 2013:097:040)
    - 2002 GI 057 - Proteccion Y Promocion De La Medicina Tradicional Conseqcuencias para La Salud Publica En Los Paises En Desarrollo - Published Material, 2002-2006; 2013:097:041 (Item 2013:097:041)
    - 2002 GI 058 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGY AND DEVELOPMENT POLICY, 2002-2007 (Box R4162)
    - 2002 GI 058 - Science, Technology and Innovation Policy; Agendas and Course Rosters, 2003-2005 - Digital, 2002-2007; 2013:097:042 (Item 2013:097:042)
    - 2002 GI 059 - (GLOBAL INCLUSION) - GI POLICY ISSUES AND ANALYSES, 2002-2005 (Box R4162)
    - 2002 GI 061 - KING'S COLLEGE LONDON (ENGALAND) - CONFLICT AND DEVELOPMENT IN INTERNATIONAL POLICY, 2002-2008 (Box R4162)
    - 2002 GI 061 - Conflict, Security and Development - Published Material, 2002-2008; 2013:097:043 (Item 2013:097:043)
    - 2002 GI 061 - Building Peace After War - Published Material, 2002-2008; 2013:097:050 (Item 2013:097:050)
    - 2003 GI 002 - COALITION FOR WOMEN'S ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT AND GLOBAL EQUALITY - IMPACTS OF REGIONAL ECONOMIC INTEGRATION IN MEXICO AND THE CARIBBEAN, 2003-2004 (Box R4162)
    - 2003 GI 003 - TUFTS UNIVERSITY - NEW MODELS FOR HEMISPHERIC INTEGRATION, 2003-2004 (Box R4162)
    - 2003 GI 004 - DUKE UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE ON IP AND WORLD TRADE, 2003-2004 (Box R4162)
    - 2003 GI 008 - SOUTH CENTRE (SWITZERLAND) - WTO NEGOTIATIONS ON INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY (3 FOLDERS), 2000-2007 (Box R4163)
    - 2003 GI 008 - The Use of Flexibilities in Trips by Developing Countries: Can They Promote Access to Medicines? - Published Material, 2000-2007; 2013:097:044 (Item 2013:097:044)
    - 2003 GI 012 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR TRADE AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT (SWITZERLAND) - IPR RELATED WTO NEGOTIATIONS, 2002-2006 (Box R4163)
    - 2003 GI 013 - ACUMEN FUND - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2000-2005 (Box R4163)
    - 2003 GI 013 - Acumen Fund "Economic and Civic Enterprise" Portfolio Launch - Audio/Visual, 2000-2005; 2013:097:045 (Item 2013:097:045)
    - 2003 GI 013 - University Inc.: The Corporate Corruption of High Education - Published Material, 2000-2005; 2013:097:046 (Item 2013:097:046)
    - 2003 GI 015 - LEADERSHIP FOR ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT INSTITUTE - GENERAL SUPPORT (1 MINUTE FOLDER and 4 and 5 SUPPL. FOLDERS), 1994-2005 (Box R4164, Box R4165)
    - RF 99010 F128 - Leadership for Environment and Development - LEADnet CD-ROM 1998 - Digital, 1994-2005; 2013:097:047 (Item 2013:097:047)
    - RF 99010 F128 - Leadership for Environment and Development - LEADnet CD-ROM 1999 - Digital, 1994-2005; 2013:097:048 (Item 2013:097:048)
    - RF 99010 F128 - LEAD International Presentation Video - 1999, 7/6/1999 - Audio/Visual, 1994-2005; 2013:097:049 (Item 2013:097:049)
- AC.2013.098: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2011; AC_2013_098; 26.2 Cubic Feet 21 standard record storage boxes, R4164-R4184; 3 standard record storage boxes, R4182-R4184
  - Global Inclusion (GI), AC_2013_098_1
    - 2003 GI 015 - Leadership for Environment and Development Institute - General Support, 1994-1995; 4 folders (Box R4164, Box R4165)
    - 2003 GI 015 - Leadership for Environment and Development Institute - General Support - Minutes, 1994-2005 (Box R4164, Box R4165)
    - 2003 GI 015 - Leadership for Environment and Development Institute - General Support - Supplementary Material, 1994-2005 (Box R4164, Box R4165)
    - 2003 GI 016 - Washburn, Jennifer - A Book on Privatization of the University, 2001-2004 (Box R4166)
    - 2003 GI 017 - International Center for Tropical Agriculture (Colombia) - Workshop on Food Safety and Transgenic Crops, 2003-2004 (Box R4166)
    - 2013.098.025 - 2003 GI 017 - International Center for Tropical Agriculture (Colombia) - Workshop on Food Safety and Transgenic Crops - Digital Material, 2003-2004; 2013.098.025 (Box R4166)
      Open for research. Access copy currently unavailable. Please see a RAC Archvist for further instruction.
    - 2003 GI 018 - United Nations Association of the United States of America - Access Discussions and Rule of Law, 2002-2005 (Box R4166)
    - 2003 GI 019 - International Crisis Group - Central African Conflict Prevention Analysis, 2003-2006 (Box R4166)
    - 2003 GI 021 - Columbia University - Managing Climate Variability to Improve Livelihoods in Asia, 2002-2008 (Box R4166)
    - 2003 GI 022 - United Nations Development Programme - 2004 Human Development Report, 2003-2004 (Box R4166)
    - 2013.098.001 - 2003 GI 022 - Human Development Report 2004: Cultural Liberty in Today's Diverse World - Published Material, 2013.098.001 (Box R4166)
    - 2003 GI 023 - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (Nigeria) - Biosafety Training, 2003-2007 (Box R4166)
    - 2003 GI 025 - United Nations University (Japan) - Call of the Earth Initiative, 2002-2006 (Box R4166)
    - 2003 GI 026 - International Peace Academy - Conflict Management in Africa and Security-Development Nexus, 2003-2005 (Box R4166)
    - 2003 GI 027 - Nuffield Foundation (England) - Workshop on Ethics of Healthcare Research in Developing Countries, 2003-2005 (Box R4166)
    - 2003 GI 028 - Global Inclusion - U.N. System in Peace and Security, 2003-2004 (Box R4166)
    - 2003 GI 029 - German Marshall Fund of the United States - Fellowship on Global Development Issues, 2003-2006 (Box R4166)
    - 2003 GI 030 - Tides Foundation - Joint Investment in Mexico of Collective Remittances, 2003-2005 (Box R4166)
    - 2003 GI 032 - Royal Institute of International Affairs (England) - United States Study Group, 2003-2005 (Box R4167)
    - 2003 GI 033 - World Affairs Council of Northern California - Conference on Borderless Giving, 2003-2004 (Box R4167)
    - 2003 GI 034 - Heartland Alliance - Building Knowledge and Capacity for Effective Bi-National Social Investment in Mexico, 2003-2005 (Box R4167)
    - 2003 GI 035 - International Centre for Trade and Sustainable Development (Switzerland) - BC Team: Global Dialogues on IP: Toward Development-Oriented IP Policy, 2003-2004 (Box R4167)
    - 2003 GI 036 - Rockefeller Foundation - Philanthropy Workshop, 1996-2006 (Box R4167)
    - 2003 GI 036 - Rockefeller Foundation - Philanthropy Workshop - Supplementary Material, 1996-2006 (Box R4167, Box 4168)
    - 2003 GI 037 - Global Inclusion - Trade Liberalization and its Impacts on Poor Farmers, 2003-2004 (Box R4169)
    - 2003 GI 038 - Social Science Research Council - Knowledge and Information Needs at the UN, 2003-2004 (Box R4169)
    - 2003 GI 039 - New York University - New Forms and Dimensions of Multilateralism, 2003-2005 (Box R4169)
    - 2003 GI 041 - Forum for Agricultural Research in Africa (Ghana) - African Biosafety Initiative, 2003-2006 (Box R4169)
    - 2003 GI 042 - Advocates Coalition for Development and Environment (Uganda) - Biotechnology and Biosafety Policies, 2003-2005 (Box R4169)
    - 2003 GI 043 - South Centre (Switzerland) - Intellectual Property Policy and Development, 2003-2006 (Box R4169)
    - 2003 GI 044 - International Centre for Trade and Sustainable Development (Switzerland) - Trade and Development Symposium in Mexico, 2003-2004 (Box R4169)
    - 2003 GI 045 - Resources for the Future - Biotechnology and Food Security in Developing Countries, 2000-2005 (Box R4169)
    - 2003 GI 047 - El Rescate - Knowledge Building and Community Transnationalism in El Salvador, 2003-2007 (Box R4169)
    - 2003 GI 048 - Harvard University - Comparative Ethnography of Transnationalism, 2003-2007 (Box R4169)
    - 2003 GI 049 - Institute of Philanthropy (England) - Philanthropy Workshop, 2003-2005 (Box R4169)
    - 2003 GI 050 - Georgetown University - Transnationalism and Development in Central American and the Caribbean, 2003-2005 (Box R4169)
    - 2003 GI 051 - International Institute for Environment and Development (England) - Millennium Development Goals Conference, 2003-2004 (Box R4169)
    - 2003 GI 052 - United Nations - UN's Relations with Civil Society, 2003-2005 (Box R4170)
    - 2003 GI 053 - Subcine - Outreach and Distribution of the "Sixth Section", 2003-2005 (Box R4170)
    - 2013_098_002 - 2003 GI 053 - The Sixth Sense - Audiovisual Material (Box R4170)
      Open for research. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - 2003 GI 054 - Human Rights Internet (Canada) - Preventing Inter-Ethnic Conflict Through Quiet Diplomacy, 2002-2009 (Box R4170)
    - 2003 GI 054 - Human Rights Internet (Canada) - Preventing Inter-Ethnic Conflict Through Quiet Diplomacy - Supplementary Material, 2002-2009 (Box R4170)
    - 2003 GI 055 - Georgetown University - Public-Private Partnerships and Sustainable Agricultural Technology in the Developing World, 2003-2008 (Box R4170)
    - 2004 GI 001 - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology (Kenya) - GMC's in Africa and Risk of Transgene Dissemination, 2000-2007 (Box R4170)
    - 2004 GI 002 - Global Policy Forum - General Support, 2003-2005 (Box R4170)
    - 2004 GI 003 - International South Group Network (Philippines) - Trade Policy and Development Issues in Africa, 2000-2005 (Box R4170)
    - 2004 GI 004 - Boston University - African Presidential Roundtable 2004, 2003-2005 (Box R4170)
    - 2004 GI 005 - International Food Policy Research Institute - Biotechnology, Agriculture and Food Security in Southern Africa, 2003-2006 (Box R4170)
    - 2004 GI 006 - WSP International (Switzerland) - Peacebuilding Forum 2004, 2003-2005 (Box R4171)
    - 2004 GI 007 - International Development Research Centre (Canada) - Research and Knowledge Systems Competition, 2003-2008 (Box R4171)
    - 2013_098_003 - 2004 GI 007 - Science and Technology Policy Development: Dialogues at the Interface - Published Material, 2003-2008 (Box R4171)
    - 2013_098_026 - 2004 GI 007 - Final Reports - Digital Material (Box R4171)
    - 2013_098_027 - 2004 GI 007 - Final Reports - Digital Material (Box R4171)
    - 2004 GI 008 - Centre for Conflict Resolution (South Africa) - Conference on the UN's Role in Africa, 2004-2007 (Box R4171)
    - 2004 GI 009 - Global Inclusion - BC Conferences - Global Dialogues on Islam and the West, 2004-2007 (Box R4171)
    - 2004 GI 010 - Africabio (South Africa) - Biotechnology Dialogue, 2001-2005 (Box R4171)
    - 2013_098_028 - 2004 GI 010 - Citizens Conference RoKS-IDRC Project - Digital Material (Box R4171)
    - 2013_098_029 - Biotechnology Communications Manual - Digital Material (Box R4171)
    - 2004 GI 011 - Center for Science in the Public Interest - Genetic Engineering in Agriculture and Regulations in Biotechnology, 2000-2006 (Box R4172)